Guide to the Records of the New York Foundling Hospital 1869-2009 MS 347
New-York Historical Society
- Series XI - Visual Materials, circa 1880-2005
  - Photomechanical reproductions of vintage prints of Foundling and other 68th St. buildings - pages removed from Avenue Magazine, 1984 September (Offsite-box 59, Folder 14)
  - 175 East 68th St. complex of buildings - interiors (few people)- photographic prints, circa 1915-1958 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 15)
  - Chapel - 175 E. 68th - interiors - photographic prints, circa 1915-1959 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 16)
  - Doctors, nurses, sisters and children - photographic prints, circa 1873-1915 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 17)
  - Doctors, nurses, sisters with children - photographic prints, circa 1915-1958 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 18)
  - Sisters and nurses with children - photographic prints, circa 1940-1960 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 19)
  - Babies and children - photographic prints, circa 1920-1965 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 20)
  - Visitors to the Foundling (mostly posing with children) - photographic prints, circa 1930-1958 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 1)
  - Christmas parties - photographic prints, circa 1942-1958 and undated (Offsite-box 60, Folder 2)
  - Bazaar and Open House - photographic prints, 1946, 1950 and undated (Offsite-box 60, Folder 3)
  - Visitors - Cardinal McIntyre, Msgrs. Reilly and McGuire, and Ted Mack - photographic prints, circa 1946, circa 1954 and undated (Offsite-box 60, Folder 4)
  - Visitors - Dionne Quintuplets - photographic prints, circa 1949-1953 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous images at 68th Street: Arrival and transportation to Foundling, women with milk, kindergarten illustration, contract signing, first anniversary of coffee shop, circa 1873-1958 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 6)
  - Reproduction of architect's drawing of 1175 Third Avenue, 1956 (Offsite-box OS 1, Folder 7)
  - 1175 Third Avenue - exteriors - photographic prints, circa 1958-1988 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 7)
  - Moving day - from 175 East 68th Street to 1175 Third Avenue - photographic prints, 1958 September 29 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 8)
  - Demolition of 175 East 68th Street complex of buildings - photographic prints (1 of 2), circa 1959 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 9)
  - Demolition of 175 East 68th Street complex of buildings - photographic prints (2 of 2), circa 1959 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 10)
  - 1175 Third Avenue chapel - photographic prints, circa 1958-1966 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 11)
  - 1175 Third Avenue interiors and roof (includes people) - photographic prints, circa 1959-1963 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 12)
  - Bazaar and Open House - photographic prints, circa 1958-1966 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 13)
  - Administration and staff events - photographic prints, circa 1958-1988 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 14)
  - Christmas parties - photographic prints, 1959-1965 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 15)
  - Doctors, nurses and sisters with children - photographic prints, circa 1958-1988 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 16)
  - Visitors - Sophie Gimbel, Fioravante G. Perrotta, Paul Newman, Howard Safir - photographic prints, circa 1959-1995 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 17)
  - Cardinal Spellman, the Advisory Board, and the Board of Managers - photographic prints, circa 1964 and undated (Offsite-box 60, Folder 18)
  - 590 Avenue of the Americas - exteriors - architect's drawing and photographic prints of completed building, 1986, 1988 and undated (Offsite-box 61, Folder 1)
  - 590 Avenue of the Americas - construction - photographic prints, 1986 September 29 - 1988 June 27 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 2)
  - 590 Avenue of the Americas - dedication, ribbon cutting, and proclamation - photographic prints, 1989 May (Offsite-box 61, Folder 3)
  - Fund raising events, award presentations (no children) - photographic prints, circa 1989-2005 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 4)
  - 590 Avenue of the Americas - Christmas - photographic prints, 1998 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous photographic prints, circa 1989-2005 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 6)
  - Signed consent forms for exhibition and publication of Yaffa photographs (1978-1980) and proposal for new Yaffa work (1994), 1978-1980 and 1994 March 23 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 7)
  - Photographic prints by Claire Yaffa, various sizes, circa 1979-1987 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 8)
  - Photographic prints by Claire Yaffa - 11x14, circa 1979-1999 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 9)
  - "Reaching Out" - Photo essay by Claire Yaffa (3 copies), 1987 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 10)
  - "Finding Their Way Home Again," "A Dying Child is Born" and "Children with AIDS" - exhibition invitations and photo essays by Claire Yaffa, 1988, 1992, 1993 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 11)
  - Photographic prints by Claire Yaffa - 8x10, circa 1998-1999 and undated (Offsite-box 61, Folder 12)
  - 8x10 photographic prints by Claire Yaffa in a folder marked "Annual Report", circa 1999 and undated (Offsite-box 61, Folder 13)
  - Kodak postive transparencies and internegatives of an exhibition of Foundling history, circa 1969-1994 (Offsite-box 62)
- Series XII - Clippings and Periodicals, 1869-2007
  The series consists of clippings of newspaper and magazine articles about the Foundling, arranged chronologically, followed by issues of periodicals with articles on the Foundling. Other clippings and periodicals may be found in other series in the collection, especially in Series IV.
  - Clippings, 1869-1938 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings -original and photocopy, circa 1879-1892 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 2)
  - Disbound scrapbook of photocopied clippings, 1869-1939 and 1948 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 3)
  - Disbound scrapbook of photocopied clippings, circa 1940-1948 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 4)
  - Disbound scrapbook of photocopied clippings, circa 1949-1959 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 5)
  - Disbound scrapbook of photocopied clippings, circa 1960-1971 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 1)
  - Photocopied clippings, circa 1985-2007 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 2)
  - "The New York Foundling Asylum" article disbound from The Rosary (unknown volume or number), 1893 December (Offsite-box 64, Folder 3)
  - The Junior Munsey - unknown volume or number - article "What New York Spends for Charities," p.64, circa 1901 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 4)
  - St. Anthony Messenger, Vol.50, No.10 - article on Foundling, p.42, 1943 March (Offsite-box 64, Folder 5)
  - Building and Modernization Age - unknown volume and number - cover story on new Foundling building, p.4, 1958 August (Offsite-box 64, Folder 6)
  - Jubilee, Vol.6, No.7 (2 copies) - article on Foundling move to new building, p.24, 1958 November (Offsite-box 64, Folder 7)
  - Jubilee, Vol.12, No.2 - article on Foundling foster child, p.10, 1964 June (Offsite-box 64, Folder 8)
  - The Journal of Practical Nursing, Vol.17, No.1 - article on Foundling licensed nurses, p.26, 1967 January (Offsite-box 64, Folder 9)
  - Image/Channel 13 Program Guide Vol.7, No.10 - article on adoption from Foundling, p.10, 1970 August (Offsite-box 64, Folder 10)
  - Children's Voice Vol.9, Nos. 2 and 3, by Child Welfare League, and 2 copies CWL calendar with Foundling art, 2000 March and May (Offsite-box 64, Folder 11)
- Series XIII - Notes Left with Children, circa 1869-1884
  The series consists of five scrapbooks of circa 1000 notes left by mothers or other guardians leaving children at the Foundling, along with transcriptions. Notes are arranged in random order in the scrapbooks.
  Children's Aid Society (New York, N.Y.)
  - Notes Left with Children, circa 1869-1871 and undated (Volume 67)
  - Notes Left with Children, circa 1869-1876 and undated (Volume 68)
  - Notes Left with Children, circa 1869-1884 and undated (Volume 69)
  - Notes Left with Children, circa 1870-1873 and undated (Volume 70)
  - Notes Left with Children, circa 1870-1872 and undated (Volume 71)
- Series XIV - Records of Children and Mothers (Restricted), 1869-1966
  This series consists of 167 volumes tracking clients of the New York Foundling Hospital. The series is divided into 9 subseries, each containing a different type of volume:
  XIV.1 - Admissions/Children's Records
  XIV.2 - Discharges
  XIV.3 - Baptisms
  XIV.4 - Boarding-Out/Foster Care Volumes
  XIV.5 - Comptroller Volumes
  XIV.6 - St. Joseph's-by-the-Sea
  XIV.7 - Mother's Records
  XIV.8 - St. Ann's Maternity Hospital
  XIV.9 - Autopsies
  Access Restrictions
  Every volume in this series is restricted.
  Records labeled as "Restricted" in this finding aid contain personal information for children cared for by the New York Foundling Hospital. Access to information in these records is by permission of the New York Foundling Hospital only. Researchers may obtain contact information for a designated specialist at the New York Foundling Hospital from the Manuscript Department of the New-York Historical Society. Guidelines currently in place for family history research at the Foundling, as determined by legal restrictions on the accessibility of adoption and foster care records, will be followed.
  Researchers who wish to view open materials will register as Manuscript users, and be allowed access to the unrestricted materials in the collection.
  - Subseries XIV.1 - Admissions/Children's Records (Restricted), 1869-1955
    The subseries consists of 15 admissions volumes 1869-1955, including 13 consecutive volumes and 2 additional volumes with some duplicate and some additional information. The volumes list children in the order they arrived, with each child given a new consecutive case number. The format of the volumes changed over the years, with different information collected. In general, the volumes give the child's name, the date of admission, date of birth, health, baptismal status, information about the parents including their religion, information about who committed the child to the Foundling, and information about the disposition of the child - his or her date of indenture, hospitalization, discharge, death, etc.
    Volume 73 includes, on the last pages, lists of colored boys and girls going to Kansas and Baltimore.
    For children listed alphabetically, see Comptroller volumes (Series XIV.5).
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol. 1 [RESTRICTED], 1869 October - 1892 December (Offsite-box 84, Volume 72)
    - Admissions [RESTRICTED], 1886 October-1896 December (Offsite-box 84, Volume 73)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol. 2 [RESTRICTED], 1893 January - 1908 September (Offsite-box 85, Volume 74)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol.3 [RESTRICTED], 1908 October - 1910 September (Offsite-box 85, Volume 75)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol.4 [RESTRICTED], 1910 September-1912 September (Offsite-box 86, Volume 76)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol.5 [RESTRICTED], 1912 September-1914 October (Offsite-box 86, Volume 77)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol.6 [RESTRICTED], 1914 October-1917 April (Offsite-box 87, Volume 78)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol.7 [RESTRICTED], 1917 April-1922 January (Offsite-box 87, Volume 79)
    - Admissions and Discharges [RESTRICTED], 1920 May-1926 July (Offsite-box 88, Volume 80)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol. 8 [RESTRICTED], 1922 January-1928 February (Offsite-box 88, Volume 81)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol. 9 [RESTRICTED], 1928 February-1930 October (Offsite-box 89, Volume 82)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol. 10 [RESTRICTED], 1930 October-1934 July (Offsite-box 89, Volume 83)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol. 11 [RESTRICTED], 1934 July-1941 December (Offsite-box 90, Volume 84)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol. 12 [RESTRICTED], 1942 January-1951 August (Offsite-box 90, Volume 85)
    - Admissions/Children's Record Vol. 13 [RESTRICTED], 1951 September-1955 February (Offsite-box 91, Volume 86)
  - Subseries XIV.2 - Discharges (Restricted), 1906-1966
    The subseries contains 9 volumes of records of children discharged from the New York Foundling Hospital, 1906-1966, with a gap between 1911 November and 1918 September. Each volume records discharges to family members or to other institutions, arranged by month. The earlier volumes also include lists of discharges due to death or indenture.
    Volume 80, in the previous subseries, also contains discharge information.
    - Discharges [RESTRICTED], 1906 October-1911 November (Offsite-box 92, Volume 87)
    - Discharges [RESTRICTED], 1918 September-1930 October (Offsite-box 92, Volume 88)
    - Discharges [RESTRICTED], 1930 November-1943 October (Offsite-box 93, Volume 89)
    - Discharges [RESTRICTED], 1943 November-1952 April (Offsite-box 93, Volume 90)
    - Discharges [RESTRICTED], 1952 May-1954 March (Offsite-box 94, Volume 91)
    - Discharges [RESTRICTED], 1954 March-1957 September (Offsite-box 94, Volume 92)
    - Discharges [RESTRICTED], 1957 September-1960 November (Offsite-box 91, Volume 93)
    - Discharges [RESTRICTED], 1960 December-1964 March (Offsite-box 95, Volume 94)
    - Discharges [RESTRICTED], 1964 April-1966 November (Offsite-box 95, Volume 95)
  - Subseries XIV.3 - Baptisms (Restricted), 1869-1945
    The subseries consists of 3 volumes of baptismal records, 1869-1945. The volumes are arranged by date, listing the name of the child, his or her case number at the Foundling, and the name of the person who performed the baptism or where it took place. The final volume includes some notations about subsequent confirmations and marriages, dating as late as circa 1962.
    Additional baptismal records may be found in the Boarding-Out Department, St. Joseph's-by-the-Sea, and St. Ann's Maternity Hospital subseries (XIV.4, XIV.6, and XIV.8 respectively).
    - Baptisms [RESTRICTED], 1869 October 27 - 1888 January 18 (Offsite-box 96, Volume 96)
    - Baptisms [RESTRICTED], 1888 January 10 - 1907 April 30 (Offsite-box 96, Volume 97)
    - Baptisms [RESTRICTED], 1907 May 1 - 1945 December 29 (Offsite-box 97, Volume 98)
  - Subseries XIV.4 - Boarding-Out/Foster Care Volumes (Restricted)
    The subseries contains several types of volumes of boarding-out and foster care records, grouped by type of volume. The various formats enable access to information from different perspectives. Text in square brackets explains each volume's organizational principle.
    - Foster Homes [alphabetical by foster parent] [RESTRICTED], circa 1874-1904 (Offsite-box 98, Volume 99)
    - Foster Homes [alphabetical by foster parent M-Z] [RESTRICTED], circa 1900-1915 (Offsite-box 100, Volume 101)
    - Foster Homes [alphabetical by foster parent] [RESTRICTED], circa 1915-1932 (Offsite-box 101, Volume 102)
    - Finance Supervision Record [chronological by child; date of birth 1884-1912, supervision 1903-1933] [RESTRICTED], 1884-1933 (Offsite-box 101, Volume 103)
    - Finance Supervision Record [chronological by child; date of birth 1888-circa 1905, supervision 1909-1927] [RESTRICTED], 1888-1927 (Offsite-box 102, Volume 104)
    - Finance Supervision Record [chronological by child; date of birth 1906-1912, supervision 1909-1932] [RESTRICTED], 1906-1932 (Offsite-box 102, Volume 105)
    - Finance Supervision Record [chronological by child; date of birth 1912-1937, supervision 1915-1944] [RESTRICTED], 1912-1944 (Offsite-box 103, Volume 106)
    - Finance Supervision Record [chronological by child; date of birth 1912-1952, supervision 1915-1959] [RESTRICTED], circa 1912-1959 (Offsite-box 103, Volume 107)
    - Placements [chronological] [RESTRICTED], 1935 October-1955 January (Offsite-box 104, Volume 108)
    - Placements [chronological] [RESTRICTED], 1941 January - 1947 May (Offsite-box 104, Volume 109)
    - Placements [chronological] [RESTRICTED], 1952 April-1956 December (Offsite-box 105, Volume 110)
    - Returns [chronological] [RESTRICTED], 1951 November-1956 December (Offsite-box 106, Volume 111)
    - Returns [chronological] [RESTRICTED], 1957 January-1958 January (Offsite-box 107, Volume 112)
    - Returns [chronological] [RESTRICTED], 1958 January-1959 January (Offsite-box 107, Volume 113)
    - Boarding-Out Department Baptism, First Holy Communion and Confirmation Book [chronological] [RESTRICTED], 1927-1957 (Offsite-box 104, Volume 114)
    - Foster Homes [alphabetical by foster parent A-L] [RESTRICTED], circa 1900-1915 (Offsite-box 99, Volume 100)
  - Subseries XIV.5 - Comptroller Volumes (Restricted)
    The subseries contains 18 volumes labeled "Comptroller." The volumes are a complete set (1874-1930) of lists of children arranged alphabetically and by year. The volumes record each child's time in an unspecified Foundling facility and provide a final disposition (discharged, transferred, indentured, died). These volumes complement the Children's Record volumes (Series XIV.1) which provide more detailed information.
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1874-1879 (Offsite-box 108, Volume 115)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1880-1885 (Offsite-box 109, Volume 116)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1885-1889 (Offsite-box 109, Volume 117)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1889-1893 (Offsite-box 109, Volume 118)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1893-1899 (Offsite-box 109, Volume 119)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1899-1904 (Offsite-box 110, Volume 120)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1904-1909 (Offsite-box 110, Volume 121)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1909-1911 (Offsite-box 110, Volume 122)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1912-1914 (Offsite-box 111, Volume 123)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1915-1916 (Offsite-box 111, Volume 124)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1917-1918 (Offsite-box 111, Volume 125)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1919-1920 (Offsite-box 112, Volume 126)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1921-1922 (Offsite-box 112, Volume 127)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 112, Volume 128)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1925-1926 (Offsite-box 112, Volume 129)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1927-1929 (Offsite-box 113, Volume 130)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1929 (Offsite-box 113, Volume 131)
    - Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1930 (Offsite-box 113, Volume 132)
  - Subseries XIV.6 - St. Joseph's-by-the-Sea (Restricted)
    The subseries consists of four volumes of records from the St. Joseph's-by-the-Sea facility in Staten Island. The facility was an overflow extension of the Foundling's facilities on 68th Street.
    - Comptroller - St. Joseph's-by-the-Sea [RESTRICTED], 1912-1924 (Offsite-box 113, Volume 113)
    - Comptroller - St. Joseph's-by-the-Sea [RESTRICTED], 1925-1928 (Offsite-box 113, Volume 134)
    - Baptisms, Communions, Confirmations - St. Joseph's-by-the-Sea [RESTRICTED], 1924-1927 (Offsite-box 114, Volume 135)
    - Baby Pavilion Returns [RESTRICTED], 1935-1955 (Offsite-box 114, Volume 136)
  - Subseries XIV.7 - Mothers' Records (Restricted)
    The subseries consists of two volumes of records of mothers who resided temporarily at the Foundling. Both volumes are arranged chronologically. There is some overlap of information in the volumes.
    - Mothers and Children [RESTRICTED], 1872-1893 (Offsite-box 114, Volume 137)
    - Mothers Register [RESTRICTED], 1875-1928 (Offsite-box 115, Volume 138)
  - Subseries XIV.8 - St. Ann's Maternity Hospital (Restricted)
    The subseries consists of 11 volumes of patients' records, followed by 86 Birth Registry volumes, followed by 2 volumes of baptismal records from St. Ann's Maternity Hospital.
    The 11 volumes of patients' records are chronological records spanning 1879-1946, with a gap between 1903 December and 1921 May, and another gap between 1926 February and 1936 January. The records 1879-1926 record the mother's name, maiden name, age, and country of birth; the father's name, age, country of birth and profession; the child's name, birthdate, and case number if applicable; a contact address; a record of payment; and sometimes the doctor's name. The records 1936-1946 record the mother's name and age, along with a detailed medical report of the labor and birth, signed by the doctor and nurse.
    The 86 Birth Registry volumes contain the birth certificate stubs of children born at St. Ann's, 1881-1946. These birth certificate stubs provide the same information as the birth certificate. The volumes are roughly chronological, with one child's certificate per page.
    The baptismal records span the years 1910-1934. The first volume (1910-1926) is organized alphabetically by child. Most of the entries are from 1910-1913, with a few added entries up to 1926. The second volume (1926-1934) is arranged chronologically.
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1879 March-1888 January (Offsite-box 115, Volume 139)
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1888 February-1903 December (Offsite-box 116, Volume 140)
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1921 May-1926 February (Offsite-box 116, Volume 141)
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1936 January-1937 April (Offsite-box 117, Volume 142)
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1937 April-1938 June (Offsite-box 117, Volume 143)
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1938 June-1939 September (Offsite-box 117, Volume 144)
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1939 September-1941 March (Offsite-box 118, Volume 145)
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1941 March-1942 July (Offsite-box 118, Volume 146)
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1942 July-1943 July (Offsite-box 118, Volume 147)
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1943 July-1945 January (Offsite-box 119, Volume 148)
    - St. Ann's Patients' Records [RESTRICTED], 1945 January-1946 February (Offsite-box 119, Volume 149)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1881 May 6 - 1883 February 11 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 150)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1882 March 10 - 1883 December 14 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 151)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1883 December 16 - 1884 December 26 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 152)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1884 December 27 - 1885 December 27 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 153)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1885 December 31 - 1886 December 23 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 154)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1886 December 25 - 1887 December 14 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 155)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1887 December 17 - 1888 December 31 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 156)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1889 January 1 - 1889 December 12 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 157)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1889 December 14 - 1890 December 17 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 158)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1890 December 18 - 1891 December 25 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 159)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1891 December 28 - 1892 December 30 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 160)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1893 January 1 - 1894 January 7 (Offsite-box 119, Volume 161)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1894 January 8 - 1895 January 8 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 162)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1895 January 10 - December 26 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 163)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1895 December 28 - 1896 December 25 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 164)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1896 December 25 - 1897 December 23 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 165)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1897 December 24 - 1898 December 30 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 166)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1899 January 3 - December 31 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 167)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1900 January 4 - December 31 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 168)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1901 January 1 - December 31 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 169)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1902 January 1 - December 31 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 170)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1903 January 1 - December 30 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 171)
    - Registry of Births [RESTRICTED], 1904 January 4 - December 31 (Offsite-box 120, Volume 172)